<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Domestic Violence Walkthrough</string>

    <string name="first">Given the rise of domestic violence which has exacerbated during COVID 19 lockdowns it is very necessary for women across all ages
        to have resources for education about these violence and how to stand up against it if you are the victim.
        \n\n
        <br>In this app we have tried to compile these resources such that it helps every women out there who is under the risk of this offense.</br>
    </string>

    <string name="info">Domestic violence can be broadly defined as a pattern of abusive behaviors by one or both partners in an intimate relationship such
        as marriage, dating, family, friends or cohabitation
        \n\n
        <br>■ It is the establishment of control and fear in a relationship through violence and other forms of abuse.</br>
        \n \n
        <br>■ The violence may involve physical abuse, sexual assault, social abuse and threats.</br>
    </string>

    <string name="info2">
       ■ The abuser tortures and controls the victim by calculated threats, intimidation, and physical violence.
        \n\n
        <br>■ In most cases, the victims are women. Children in homes where there is domestic violence are also abused or neglected.</br>
       \n\n
        <br>■ Domestic violence is a CRIME and you must seek help.</br>
    </string>


    <string name="law1">
        Protection of Women against Domestic Violence Act, 2005
        \n\n
        <br>■ This is an act of the Indian Parliament enacted to protect women from Domestic Violence.</br>
        \n \n
        <br>■ It prohibits a wide range of Physical, Sexual, Emotional and Economical abuse against women
and all these are broadly defined under the Act.</br>
        \n \n
        <br>■ This law is to guarantee that women don’t get kicked out of their own house and can support themselves if they have been abused.</br>
    </string>

    <string name="law2">
        Section 498A of the IPC (Indian Penal Code)
        \n\n
        <br>■ This is a Criminal Law, which applies to husbands or family members of husband who are merciless to women. This harassment can be of any type either Physical or Mental. </br>
        \n \n
        <br>■ It also includes any and all intentional behaviours against a women which force the women to attempt suicide or risk to life or grave injury or risk to limb or overall health.</br>
         \n \n
        <br>■
A complaint can also be lodged under Section 498A of Indian Penal Code for Cruelty which also falls under DOMESTIC VIOLENCE.</br>

    </string>

    <string name="law3">
        Dowry Prohibition Act, 1961
        \n\n
        <br>■ This is a Criminal Law that punishes the giving and taking of Dowry. The tradition of dowry itself is banned under the Dowry Prohibition Act, 1961.</br>
        \n \n
        <br>■  According to this law, gives, takes or even demands dowry, they can be imprisoned for a half year (i.e. for 6 months) or they can be fined upto Five Thousand Rupees.</br>
    </string>

    <string name="helpline">
        <br>Nation Commission for Women: 7217735372</br>
        \n\n
        <br>Domestic Voilence Helpline Pune: 8793988814</br>
         \n\n
        <br>All India Womens Confrence Delhi: (011) 23389680</br>
         \n\n
        <br>Womens Helpline Banglore: 080-22943225</br>
         \n\n
        <br>Womens Helpline Mumbai:022-22633333</br>
    </string>


</resources>